When it came down to the Nazis and their military technology
You can't deny that they were next level
They made mortars the size of blue whales that shot shells as big as rhinos
Built an artillery cannon so big and powerful
That the Nazis broke it down themselves, as they were afraid the Soviets would capture and use it against them
And they even worked on a prototype defray
A ray weapon that could kill the engine of an airplane and its pilot
With one simple click
The Nazis were spearheading massive and ungodly new means of warfare
And among those many plants of mass destruction
Was one that, luckily, never saw the light of day
At least, not by this fedora-wearing fella
Meet the hero of its time, or the main villain, Wu Fei
Historically, facts, part four. It's